{
    "subject": "resource/SexyMandarin",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundedBy",
    "object": "resource/Michael_Gleissner",
    "human_readable": "SexyMandarin was founded by Michael Gleissner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9880287051200867,
            "question": "Is Michael Gleissner the founder of SexyMandarin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9878054857254028,
            "question": "Is SexyMandarin a company founded by Michael Gleissner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9144737124443054,
            "question": "By whom was SexyMandarin established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.91341233253479,
            "question": "Who founded SexyMandarin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8571746945381165,
            "question": "What is the name of the founder of SexyMandarin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114749789237976,
            "question": "Can you tell me the founder of SexyMandarin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7352586984634399,
            "question": "Michael Gleissner is known for founding which company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.698861300945282,
            "question": "What company was created by Michael Gleissner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4811459183692932,
            "question": "Who is responsible for starting SexyMandarin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4427794814109802,
            "question": "What company did Michael Gleissner found?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=SexyMandarin was founded by Michael Gleissner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7857_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is responsible for starting SexyMandarin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7857_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What company was created by Michael Gleissner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7857_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Gleissner is known for founding which company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7857_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7857_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\nThe provided text states: \"It was founded by Kaoru Kikuchi and Michael Gleissner in December 2011.\"  This directly confirms that Michael Gleissner was one of the founders of SexyMandarin."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention \"Michael Gleissner\" as one of the founders of SexyMandarin (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7857/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7857/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt).\n* The documents also mention \"Kaoru Kikuchi\" as another founder of SexyMandarin (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7857/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7857/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt).\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that SexyMandarin was founded by Michael Gleissner. The correct answer is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that \"SexyMandarin was founded by Kaoru Kikuchi and Michael Gleissner in December 2011,\" which supports the query that SexyMandarin was indeed founded by Michael Gleissner."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}